{"questionlist":[
{"cardfront":"El arte",
"cardback":"art"
},
{"cardfront":"La biologia",
"cardback":"Biology"
},
{"cardfront":"El colegio",
"cardback":"School"
},
{"cardfront":"La computacion",
"cardback":"Computer Class"
},
{"cardfront":"El Espanol",
"cardback":"Spanish Class"
},
{"cardfront":"La Historia",
"cardback":"History"
},
{"cardfront":"El horario",
"cardback":"Scedule"
},
{"cardfront":"El Ingles",
  "cardback":"English"
},
{"cardfront":"Las Matematicas",
  "cardback":"Mathmemics"
},
{"cardfront":"La musica",
  "cardback":"Music"
},
{"cardfront":"alo",
  "cardback":"Hello(telephone)"
},
{"cardfront":"cual?",
  "cardback":"Which ones?"
},
{"cardfront":"La Direccion",
  "cardback":"Internet/Mail"
},
{"cardfront":"El Numero de telefono",
  "cardback":"Communication Numbers"
},
{"cardfront":"El telefono",
  "cardback":"telephone"
},
{"cardfront":"La Blusa",
  "cardback":"Blouse"
},
{"cardfront":"El Calcetin",
  "cardback":"Sock"
},
{"cardfront":"La camisa",
  "cardback":"Shirt"
},
{"cardfront":"La camiseta",
  "cardback":"Jersy,tshirt"
},
{"cardfront":"La falda",
  "cardback":"Skirt"
},
{"cardfront":"Los jeans",
  "cardback":"Jeans"
},
{"cardfront":"El pantalon",
  "cardback":"Pants"
},
{"cardfront":"La Ropa",
  "cardback":"Clothing"
},
{"cardfront":"El Zapato",
  "cardback":"Shoes"
},
{"cardfront":"Amarillo/a",
  "cardback":"yellow"
},
{"cardfront":"Azul",
  "cardback":"Blue"
},
{"cardfront":"Blanco/a",
  "cardback":"white"
},
{"cardfront":"gris",
  "cardback":"grey"
},
{"cardfront":"negro/a",
  "cardback":"black"
},
{"cardfront":"rojo/a",
  "cardback":"red"
},
{"cardfront":"Verde",
  "cardback":"Green"
},
{"cardfront":"La arroba",
  "cardback":"@"
},
{"cardfront":"La Computadora",
  "cardback":"Computer"
},
{"cardfront":"El disco",
  "cardback":"CD-ROM"
},
{"cardfront":"LA impresora",
  "cardback":"Lazer Printer"
},
{"cardfront":"La pantalla",
  "cardback":"Screen"
},
{"cardfront":"El raton",
  "cardback":"Mouse"
},
{"cardfront":"El teclado",
  "cardback":"Keyboard"
},
{"cardfront":"EL Domingo",
  "cardback":"Sunday"
},
{"cardfront":"El Jueves",
  "cardback":"Thursday"
},
{"cardfront":"El Lunes",
  "cardback":"Monday"
},
{"cardfront":"El Martes",
  "cardback":"Tuesday"
},
{"cardfront":"El Miercoles",
  "cardback":"Wednesday"
},
{"cardfront":"El sabado",
  "cardback":"Saturday"
},
{"cardfront":"El viernes",
  "cardback":"Friday"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
  "cardback":"E"
}
]}
